<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Introduction</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am Stefano Grasso, since July 2022 I work as a Multiplexed Synthetic Biology Scientist in the newly established Biofoundry of (Lesaffre) in Lille (France).&#xA;Until May 2022, I was Post-doc at the Centro de Biotecnología y Genómica de Plantas (CBGP) within the Universidad Politécnica de Madrid (UPM). From 2015 to 2020 I was a Marie Curie fellow within the ITN project ProteinFactory, and a PhD student at UMCG (Groninen University, NL) and DSM Food Specialties B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research interests</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/research_interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/research_interests/</guid>
      <description>I have very broad research interestes all pointing into the direction of fusing (bio)informatics and (bio)technology, in what is at the moment called Synthetic biology. Main interests are in (but not limited to): protein secretion, strain development and optimization, protein analyses and annotation, genomic annotation, comparative proteomic and genomic analyses, development of prediction tools, synthetic biology and genetic engineering.&#xA;I also have a very broad thecnical and scientifc knowledge and experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/consulting/</guid>
      <description>I offer tailoerd solution for any necessity in the broader field of biotechnology and bioinformatics (both wet- and dry-lab). Due to my hybrid experience I can assist you in the wet-lab part, always taking into account all the other aspects. Similarly, I can provide advice and support for in silico projects by always having in mind the experimental counterpart.&#xA;Some examples of offered services (but not limited to): Design and development of custom tools and software for prediction and analyses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/software/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of bioinformatics tools I developed:&#xA;GP4 (Gram-Positive Protein Prediction Pipeline) is protein subcellular localization meta-prediction tool tailored for Gram+ Bacteria and implementing an expert system predictor. It is free to use and can be used as a webserver or downloaded from its website (Currently under manteinance - not avaialble as webserver, plase refer to github and the publication).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/cv/</guid>
      <description>You can download my full CV here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/links/</guid>
      <description>DR-i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stefano Grasso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/index-conflicted-copy-2024-08-11-125234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/index-conflicted-copy-2024-08-11-125234/</guid>
      <description>Personal and professional website of Stefano Grasso. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>Send me an email!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
